## Jon Brown

Home: 207 – 985 – 3765 • Cell: N/A 6 Katie Lane, Arundel Maine 04046. USA E-Mail: jon@jonbrown.org or jonbrown2@mac.com Website: http://www.jonbrown.org

# Objective

To offer my services and expertise as a computer consultant, IT professional; Graphic artist or web designer, I would like to work for a company that will challenge my skills and push me towards new horizons. I work well with other people and I am a real "team player". I do not think I have the market cornered on the things I can do, however I enjoy my work and I have a real passion for the arts.

# Education

# Kennebunk High School, Kennebunk, Maine

College Preparatory Curriculum

One Year Typing (speed 30 - 50 wpm)

One-Year Microsoft Office Course (certificate)

## Franklin Pierce University, Rindge, New Hampshire

Graphic Design & Computer Animation Major

Fine arts and Stained glass Minor

**BA Graphic Communications** 

**BA** Computer Animation

Office Administration (1 Semester Course)

Public Speaking (1 Year Course)

## York County Community College, Wells, Maine

Office Administration (certificate)
Business Administration (certificate)

Work Experience

## **English Instructor / Professor**

Joy English School

Taichung County, Taichung City, Taiwan 414 Contact: Wendy Chung (0423365956)

#### **English Instructor / Computer Consultant**

Wonderland

Hwajung Dong, Goyang Shi, Kyunggi Do,

Ilsan, South Korea

Contact: Colleen (0163591246)

#### English Teacher / System Admin (Jr.) Mongolia

English Language Institute San Dimas, California, USA

Contact: Tim Hunsberger (97611310519)

(2001-2002)

(1993-1997)

(1997-2001)

(2005-2006)

(2003-2005)

(2002-2003)

Graphic Design and Web Design Professor

(2001-2002)

York County Technical College, 112 College Dr, Wells, Maine 04090 - 5341, America

Contact: Ed Stone (2076469282)

**Graphic Designer and Web Designer** 

(2001-2002)

Online Design Inc,

Biddeford, Maine, America

Contact: Rix Kordsmeier (4068212292)

**Computer Technician and Supervisor** 

(1998-2001)

Franklin Pierce University,

20 College Rd, Rindge, New Hampshire

03461 - 0060, America

Contact: Richard Block (6038994324)

Graphic Designer

(1998-1999)

New England Business Systems INC.

Peterborough, New Hampshire,

03461 – 0060, America

Contact: Bill Harris (8002259528)

**Classified Ad Graphic Artist** 

(1998 June-Aug)

York County Coast Star Newspaper, 198 Maine St, Kennebunk, Maine, 04046. America

04046, America

Temp Job

# Accomplishments

## **Graphic Design Award**

Franklin Pierce University,

20 College Rd, Rindge, New Hampshire

03461 – 0060, America

Contact: Robert Deriks (6038994324)

#### **Batchelors Degree Graphic Communications: Suma Kum Laude**

Franklin Pierce University,

20 College Rd, Rindge, New Hampshire

03461 – 0060, America

Contact: Robert Deriks (6038994324)

## References

# Available upon request.